export default {
  id: 'low_1006_5_1b',
  name: '상용한자(5학년-1/한자찾기)',
  data: [
    { question: '독:あたい/음:か', answer: ['価'] },
    { question: '독:옳을/음:か', answer: ['可'] },
    { question: '독:かり/음:か、[け]', answer: ['仮'] },
    { question: '독:새길/음:かん', answer: ['刊'] },
    { question: '독:みき/음:かん', answer: ['幹'] },
    { question: '독:へ(る)、へ(らす)/음:げん', answer: ['減'] },
    { question: '독:외울/음:こう', answer: ['講'] },
    { question: '독:낱/음:こ', answer: ['個'] },
    { question: '독:い(る)/음:きょ', answer: ['居'] },
    { question: '독:물건/음:けん', answer: ['件'] },
    { question: '독:검사할/음:けん', answer: ['検'] },
    { question: '독:격식/음:かく、[こう]', answer: ['格'] },
    { question: '독:いさぎよ(い)/음:けつ', answer: ['潔'] },
    { question: '독:へ(る)/음:けい、きょう', answer: ['経'] },
    { question: '독:さかい/음:きょう、[けい]', answer: ['境'] },
    { question: '독:たがや(す)/음:こう', answer: ['耕'] },
    { question: '독:ゆえ/음:こ', answer: ['故'] },
    { question: '독:す(ぎる)、す(ごす)、あやま(つ)、あやま(ち)/음:か', answer: ['過'] },
    { question: '독:な(れる)、な(らす)/음:かん', answer: ['慣'] },
    { question: '독:쇳돌/음:こう', answer: ['鉱'] },
    { question: '독:かま(える)、かま(う)/음:こう', answer: ['構'] },
    { question: '독:글귀/음:く', answer: ['句'] },
    { question: '독:ひさ(しい)/음:きゅう、[く]', answer: ['久'] },
    { question: '독:옛/음:きゅう', answer: ['旧'] },
    { question: '독:む(れる)、む(れ)、むら/음:ぐん', answer: ['群'] },
    { question: '독:문서/음:けん', answer: ['券'] },
    { question: '독:법/음:き', answer: ['規'] },
    { question: '독:고를/음:きん', answer: ['均'] },
    { question: '독:금할/음:きん', answer: ['禁'] },
    { question: '독:よ(る)、よ(せる)/음:き', answer: ['寄'] },
    { question: '독:もと、もとい/음:き', answer: ['基'] },
    { question: '독:わざ/음:ぎ', answer: ['技'] },
    { question: '독:능할/음:のう', answer: ['能'] },
    { question: '독:둥글/음:だん、[とん]', answer: ['団'] },
    { question: '독:た(つ)、ことわ(る)/음:だん', answer: ['断'] },
    { question: '독:か(す)/음:たい', answer: ['貸'] },
    { question: '독:큰/음:とく', answer: ['徳'] },
    { question: '독:みちび(く)/음:どう', answer: ['導'] },
    { question: '독:ひと(り)/음:どく', answer: ['独'] },
    { question: '독:구리/음:どう', answer: ['銅'] },
    { question: '독:간략할/음:りゃく', answer: ['略'] },
    { question: '독:거느릴/음:りょう', answer: ['領'] },
    { question: '독:と(める)、と(まる)/음:りゅう、[る]', answer: ['留'] },
    { question: '독:わた/음:めん', answer: ['綿'] },
    { question: '독:ゆめ/음:む', answer: ['夢'] },
    { question: '독:はか/음:ぼ', answer: ['墓'] },
    { question: '독:호반/음:ぶ、む', answer: ['武'] },
    { question: '독:무역할/음:ぼう', answer: ['貿'] },
    { question: '독:つと(める)、つと(まる)/음:む', answer: ['務'] },
    { question: '독:まよ(う)/음:めい', answer: ['迷'] },
    { question: '독:ふせ(ぐ)/음:ぼう', answer: ['防'] },
    { question: '독:おか(す)/음:はん', answer: ['犯'] },
    { question: '독:고깔/말씀/음:べん', answer: ['弁'] },
    { question: '독:たも(つ)/음:ほ', answer: ['保'] },
    { question: '독:むく(いる)/음:ほう', answer: ['報'] },
    { question: '독:회복할/음:ふく', answer: ['復'] },
    { question: '독:겹칠/음:ふく', answer: ['複'] },
    { question: '독:며느리/음:ふ', answer: ['婦'] },
    { question: '독:と(む)、とみ/음:ふ、[ふう]', answer: ['富'] },
    { question: '독:ほとけ/음:ぶつ', answer: ['仏'] },
    { question: '독:くら(べる)/음:ひ', answer: ['比'] },
    { question: '독:아닐/음:ひ', answer: ['非'] },
    { question: '독:そな(える)、そな(わる)/음:び', answer: ['備'] },
    { question: '독:こ(える)、こえ、こ(やす)、こ(やし)/음:ひ', answer: ['肥'] },
    { question: '독:まず(しい)/음:ひん、びん', answer: ['貧'] },
    { question: '독:스승/음:し', answer: ['師'] },
    { question: '독:조사할/음:さ', answer: ['査'] },
    { question: '독:に(る)/음:じ', answer: ['似'] },
    { question: '독:かう/음:し', answer: ['飼'] },
    { question: '독:집/음:しゃ', answer: ['舎'] },
    { question: '독:あやま(る)/음:しゃ', answer: ['謝'] },
    { question: '독:す(い)/음:さん', answer: ['酸'] },
    { question: '독:형상/음:じょう', answer: ['状'] },
    { question: '독:つね、とこ/음:じょう', answer: ['常'] },
    { question: '독:모양/음:ぞう', answer: ['像'] },
    { question: '독:차례/음:じょ', answer: ['序'] },
    { question: '독:もう(ける)/음:せつ', answer: ['設'] },
    { question: '독:した/음:ぜつ', answer: ['舌'] },
    { question: '독:성품/음:せい、しょう', answer: ['性'] },
    { question: '독:いきお(い)/음:せい', answer: ['勢'] },
    { question: '독:세금/음:ぜい', answer: ['税'] },
    { question: '독:본디/음:そ、す', answer: ['素'] },
    { question: '독:무리/음:ぞく', answer: ['属'] },
    { question: '독:そこ(なう)、そこ(ねる)/음:そん', answer: ['損'] },
    { question: '독:ひき(いる)/음:りつ、そつ', answer: ['率'] },
    { question: '독:보낼/음:ゆ', answer: ['輸'] },
    { question: '독:さず(ける)、さず(かる)/음:じゅ', answer: ['授'] },
    { question: '독:おさ(める)、おさ(まる)/음:しゅう、[しゅ]', answer: ['修'] },
    { question: '독:の(べる)/음:じゅつ', answer: ['述'] },
    { question: '독:재주/음:じゅつ', answer: ['術'] }
  ]
}
